{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Baby Proofing Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40190/":{"taskOID":40190,"originalTaskOID":40190,"setID":498,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4662,"questionDisplayText":"Types of service","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of childproofing service are you interested in?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4976,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Purchasing of products only","answerDisplayText":"Purchasing of products only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3278,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Installation of products only","answerDisplayText":"Installation of products only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1088,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Both purchase and installation of products","answerDisplayText":"Both purchase and installation of products","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4661,"questionDisplayText":"Types of Products Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which type of products do you need? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5537,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Securing of doors, drawers and appliances","answerDisplayText":"Securing of doors, drawers and appliances","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2769,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Gates and guards for doors and windows","answerDisplayText":"Gates and guards for doors and windows","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4790,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Pool, door and gate alarms","answerDisplayText":"Pool, door and gate alarms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6989,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Window covering cords","answerDisplayText":"Window covering cords","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1371,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Childproof electrical outlets and devices","answerDisplayText":"Childproof electrical outlets and devices","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2458,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Fire escape ladders","answerDisplayText":"Fire escape ladders","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1646,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Corner and edge guards","answerDisplayText":"Corner and edge guards","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6424,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Toilet lid locks","answerDisplayText":"Toilet lid locks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4258,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"No-tip furniture brackets","answerDisplayText":"No-tip furniture brackets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2194,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Electronic equipment guards","answerDisplayText":"Electronic equipment guards","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1370,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Childproof bottle caps","answerDisplayText":"Childproof bottle caps","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5153,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Removable child safety fence","answerDisplayText":"Removable child safety fence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8031,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4663,"questionDisplayText":"Range of ages in home","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the range of ages in your home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":260,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"0-3","answerDisplayText":"0-3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":453,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"3-5","answerDisplayText":"3-5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":521,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5-7","answerDisplayText":"5-7","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":553,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"7 and up","answerDisplayText":"7 and up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4662,"questionDisplayText":"Types of service","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of childproofing service are you interested in?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4976,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Purchasing of products only","answerDisplayText":"Purchasing of products only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3278,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Installation of products only","answerDisplayText":"Installation of products only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1088,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Both purchase and installation of products","answerDisplayText":"Both purchase and installation of products","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4976,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Purchasing of products only","answerDisplayText":"Purchasing of products only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3278,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Installation of products only","answerDisplayText":"Installation of products only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1088,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Both purchase and installation of products","answerDisplayText":"Both purchase and installation of products","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4661,"questionDisplayText":"Types of Products Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which type of products do you need? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5537,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Securing of doors, drawers and appliances","answerDisplayText":"Securing of doors, drawers and appliances","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2769,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Gates and guards for doors and windows","answerDisplayText":"Gates and guards for doors and windows","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4790,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Pool, door and gate alarms","answerDisplayText":"Pool, door and gate alarms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6989,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Window covering cords","answerDisplayText":"Window covering cords","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1371,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Childproof electrical outlets and devices","answerDisplayText":"Childproof electrical outlets and devices","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2458,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Fire escape ladders","answerDisplayText":"Fire escape ladders","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1646,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Corner and edge guards","answerDisplayText":"Corner and edge guards","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6424,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Toilet lid locks","answerDisplayText":"Toilet lid locks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4258,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"No-tip furniture brackets","answerDisplayText":"No-tip furniture brackets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2194,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Electronic equipment guards","answerDisplayText":"Electronic equipment guards","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1370,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Childproof bottle caps","answerDisplayText":"Childproof bottle caps","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5153,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Removable child safety fence","answerDisplayText":"Removable child safety fence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8031,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5537,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Securing of doors, drawers and appliances","answerDisplayText":"Securing of doors, drawers and appliances","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2769,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Gates and guards for doors and windows","answerDisplayText":"Gates and guards for doors and windows","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4790,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Pool, door and gate alarms","answerDisplayText":"Pool, door and gate alarms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6989,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Window covering cords","answerDisplayText":"Window covering cords","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1371,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Childproof electrical outlets and devices","answerDisplayText":"Childproof electrical outlets and devices","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2458,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Fire escape ladders","answerDisplayText":"Fire escape ladders","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1646,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Corner and edge guards","answerDisplayText":"Corner and edge guards","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6424,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Toilet lid locks","answerDisplayText":"Toilet lid locks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4258,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"No-tip furniture brackets","answerDisplayText":"No-tip furniture brackets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2194,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Electronic equipment guards","answerDisplayText":"Electronic equipment guards","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1370,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Childproof bottle caps","answerDisplayText":"Childproof bottle caps","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5153,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Removable child safety fence","answerDisplayText":"Removable child safety fence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8031,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4663,"questionDisplayText":"Range of ages in home","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the range of ages in your home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":260,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"0-3","answerDisplayText":"0-3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":453,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"3-5","answerDisplayText":"3-5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":521,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5-7","answerDisplayText":"5-7","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":553,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"7 and up","answerDisplayText":"7 and up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":260,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"0-3","answerDisplayText":"0-3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":453,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"3-5","answerDisplayText":"3-5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":521,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5-7","answerDisplayText":"5-7","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":553,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"7 and up","answerDisplayText":"7 and up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"__cache./api/resource/task/40190/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40190,"taskName":"Child Proofing - Install","taskDescription":"Childproof a Living Space","xmTaskDescriptor":"Baby Proofing Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":120,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Child, safety, handymen, childproof, guard","textMessagingName":"Childproof","rolloverLongDesc":"Typically includes assessment of risk factors \u0026 either their removal or mitigation through the installation of accessories such as outlet covers \u0026 special latches. May also include recommendations about dangerous furniture \u0026 how \u0026 where potentially hazardous materials should be stored.","rolloverShortDesc":"Make a living space safer for small children.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Childproof a Living Space.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Child \u0026 Baby Proofing Services \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":40,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Child-proofing Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Child Proofing - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Childproofing Project","urlName":"Child-Proofing-Install","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Baby Proofing Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Cost Info, Reviews","searchKeywords":"Child, handymen, handy, handyman, family, childproofing, childproof, safety","emcCategoryOid":-12039,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":498,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}